There is a woman outside there, you are pregnant.
Right now, you are due to deliver a baby.
This is almost three children that when you deliver them,
when they are just a baby, they die.
When they just make... - they die immediately.
So, you have this one now. The child is due. This is a baby boy.
She is outside there, under the canopy.
Jesus loves you.
Here we can see the woman the prophecy concerned coming forward
from under the canopies at the overflow congregation.
Just as the man of God had prophecied,
the woman was sitting outside the auditorium under the canopies and was pregnant.
She makes her way up the stairs, heading inside the main auditorium of the church
to honour and confirm the word of prophecy,
that there was a woman pregnant with a baby boy outside the church, her delivery was due.
And in the past, she had given birth to children who had all died shortly after birth.
Inside the church, she moves towards the altar to meet Prophet T.B. Joshua.
- This is your wife?
- Yes, sir.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
Prophecy Confirmation
The reason why I said well done is that Jesus has the solution.
Well done.
Thank you, sir.
Prophecy Confirmation
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Stretching his right hand, the man of God prays for her in the name of Jesus Christ.
Immediately, there is a visible reaction in the woman,
as Prophet T.B. Joshua offers prayer under the influence of the Holy Spirit.
This is prayer in the power of the Holy Spirit right now.
Watch what's happening!
Watch and see her expression!
You can tell something extraordinary is happening to her.
From the look on her face, you can see she is not comfortable.
Look at her stomach jumping!
Watch your screen, see what's happening! Her stomach is moving!
This is the result of the prayer offered by Prophet T.B. Joshua just moments ago.
The child is turning.
It is the position the baby has been coming out with.
Before that baby was coming out, a lot of wrestle.
The doctor had been wrestling, the nurse had been wrestling.
Before the baby came out, it had become tired and died.
But this time around, it has to reposition.
It will come out straight.
It's turning; before now, it was bottom.
But it's now turning right. It's coming out with the head.
When it finishes, you can take her to the hospital.
How do you feel? What is happening in your stomach?
My baby is rotating.
The baby is rotating? How?
Because you are the one carrying the baby. You know what's happening in your stomach.
The baby is rotating, turning like this.
- It is turning the body?
- Yes.
- Rotating like this?
IMPOSSIBLE: Baby Turns In Womb As Pastor Prays!!!
Any moment from now, you will feel something pushing,
something will come out like a little water burst; after that, the road is open.
Amen. Thank You, Jesus!
IMPOSSIBLE: Baby Turns In Womb As Pastor Prays!!!
The thing has come down now - the water I am talking about!
You can see the baby stopped moving
because it has finally repositioned.
She is free. Ok, take her to the toilet.
Thank You, Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
After receiving prayer and the Anointed Wristband from Prophet T.B. Joshua,
the lady is led out of the main auditorium to go to the lavatories
and release the water that the man of God had prophesied about.
Waving and smiling, she is followed by her husband.
As she moves through the church, climbing up a short flight of stairs
she enters the lavatories, and proceeds to pass out the fluid.
Healed In Jesus' Name
The woman came back with her bouncing baby boy to The Synagogue, Church Of All Nations
to testify to the glory of God in confirmation of the prophecy
given to her by Prophet T.B. Joshua that she would deliver a baby boy without an operation.
Praise the Lord!
Emmanuel!
(God with us - Matthew 1:23)
Our names are Mr & Mrs Kingsley.
The man of God prophesied to me that there was a woman here
who had delivered three children.
The first one survived, the second one died, and the third one died.
He said that the woman was outside, under the canopy,
and that the woman should come inside.
There is a woman outside there, you are pregnant.
Right now, you are due to deliver a baby.
This is almost three children that when you deliver them,
when they are just a baby, they die.
Immediately, I came inside and the man of God prophesied to me
that I had a baby boy in my womb
and the problem that caused the death of the children was prolonged labour.
And he said that I should go; the problem was solved.
He gave me the Anointed Wristband
and he said that something would burst from my stomach.
When he said that, he said I should go and that this baby would not die.
What is happening in your stomach?
My baby is rotating.
- It is turning his body?
- Yes.
- Rotating like this?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Any moment from now, you will feel something pushing,
something will come out like a little water burst; after that, the road is open.
Amen. Thank You, Jesus!
Everything the man of God said has come to pass.
After the prophecy, we left and went back to Imo State.
When we got to Imo State, I went to my doctor,
and my doctor said that he would book me for an operation
because of the problem I had been having.
I said, "No", that the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua has broken the yoke
and that I was not going to do any operation.
I used the Anointing Wristband and prayed.
I told the doctor that I was not going to deliver this baby through an operation.
Immediately, he left me.
In the morning, I used the Anointing Wristband and prayed.
I put it on my stomach and said that
as far as the man of God prophesied that my baby was not going to die,
my baby is safe and secured by the hand of the Almighty God.
Before the doctor came, I delivered my baby so fast, without any operation
And this is the baby boy.
You can see that he's a baby boy.
Everything the man of God prophesied to my life is true.
The second baby died.
I didn't come out with the baby.
The third one died inside the labour room.
That was the prophecy I received.
And you can see that Prophet T.B. Joshua prophesied this and it has manifested.
I am alive. My baby is alive.
Emmanuel!
(God with us - Matthew 1:23)
Praise the Lord!
Praise the living God!
Emmanuel!
(God with us - Matthew 1:23)
Our names are Mr & Mrs Kingsley; we came from Imo state, Nigeria.
During the second service, the man of God prophesied
that there was a woman outside, under the canopy,
that whenever she delivered a baby, the baby would cry and then die.
When I heard the prophecy, I told my wife that this was our prophecy and
that the Lord had remembered us.
Do you remember what I told you that day? How I made a joke...
You said, "Well done, Oga".
I said, "Well done, Oga".
Yes, sir.
What's the meaning of that?
For a job well done because the stomach was too big.
After the prayer, I thank God today
because the Almighty God has used Prophet T.B. Joshua
to bring laughter to my family and now, I have a baby boy.
He's my first son because the first son I had died.
But I am happy today because I have a son in the house.
Thank You, Jesus!
RV: Mel Flowers 30/04/2019